<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecipeBook</string>
    <string name="welcome">Recipes by Ferdinand</string>
    <string name="recipe1">Adobo</string>
    <string name="recipe2">Sinigang</string>
    <string name="recipe3">Pares</string>
    <string name="recipe4">Dinuguan</string>
    <string name="recipe5">Menudo</string>
    <string name="recipe6">Giniling</string>
    <string name="recipe_list">Recipe List</string>
    <string name="recipe">Recipe:</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about the recipe.</string>

    <!--RECIPE FOR ADOBO-->
    <string name="adobo_recipe">
        Start by marinating the chicken in soy sauce and garlic. This process usually
        takes 1 hour to 12 hours depending on how flavorful you want the dish to be.
        The next step is to separate the chicken from the marinade. Make sure to set the marinade
        aside because it will be used later on. Pan-fry the chicken pieces for 1 minute per side.
        Pour marinade into the pot and add water. Let it boil. This process takes 20 to 25 minutes
        depending on the quality of the chicken. After stewing, add vinegar and continue to
        cook for another 10 minutes and adding sugar and salt.
    </string>

    <!--RECIPE FOR SINIGANG-->
    <string name="sinigang_recipe">
        Traditional sinigang is cooked plainly by boiling all the ingredients together.
        Start by pouring the tamarind broth into a cookware of your choice. Deep and wide pots are perfect for this.
        Boil the liquid and then add some onion and tomato. This will add flavor to the broth.
        This is also the proper time to add the pork belly. Make sure to cover your pot so that the liquid can boil quickly.
        The first batch of veggies to add are daikon radish and eggplants. Some people also add their string beans at this point
        if they want it to be extra soft later on. I prefer mine to be a bit crisp. After 5 minutes of cooking in low heat (above simmering temp),
        add the long green peppers, string beans, remaining tomatoes, and okra and continue cooking for 3 minutes.
    </string>

    <!--RECIPE FOR PARES-->
    <string name="pares_recipe">
        It is best to always have the beef stock ready before cooking pares. This is the soup that goes with it.
        Cooking beef pares is easier when using a pressure cooker. This helps tenderize the beef quickly.
        Start by sauteing onion, garlic, and ginger. These aromatics brings-in flavor and aroma to your dish.
        Make sure that the onion softens. This makes it sweeter. Add the beef and continue to saute until it browns.
        Pour-in water and then add a piece of Knorr Beef Cube and 2 pieces of star anise. Pressure cook for 15 minutes.
        You can cook it longer up to 20 minutes, but make sure that the beef is still intact. Add sugar and season with salt and ground black pepper.
    </string>

    <!--RECIPE FOR DINUGUAN-->
    <string name="dinuguan_recipe">
        Start by sautéing garlic and onion. Make sure that the onion softens before adding the pork. Saute the meat until it turns light brown.
        Cook it until it turns light brown. Feel free to add innards. Tenderize the pork by boiling. Pour water, cover the pot,
        and cook in low heat until tender. Adding a piece of pork cube (bouillon) is a big help to make the dish taste meatier.
        Pour the pork blood while stirring and cook it for at least 8 minutes to make sure that it is fully done. Add vinegar and the remaining ingredients.
    </string>

    <!--RECIPE FOR MENUDO-->
    <string name="menudo_recipe">
        Combine the pork, soy sauce and lemon in a bowl. Mix well and let it stay for at least 1 hour. It will be better to store
        the bowl inside the refrigerator while you marinate to avoid contamination. Make sure to cover the bowl before doing this.
        Take the pork out of the fridge 15 minutes before cooking. Start to saute the garlic and onion.
        Once the onions are soft, add the marinated pork and cook until it browns. Add tomato sauce (you can also use crushed tomatoes),
        water (or beef broth), and bay leaves. We are using dried bay leaves for this recipe. Cover and simmer until
        the meat gets tender — which is usually 40 to 60 minutes depending on the quality of the meat. Once the meat is done,
        it is time to add the sliced liver. You can add the liver fresh or you can saute it first in ginger and garlic to make it
        less gamey. Add the veggies after this step and continue to cook for a few more minutes.
    </string>

    <!--RECIPE FOR GINILING-->
    <string name="giniling_recipe">
        Heat a cooking pot and pour-in the cooking oil.
        When the oil is hot enough, put-in the garlic and sauté until the color turns light brown.
        Add the onions and sauté until the texture becomes soft.
        Put-in the ground pork and cook for 5 minutes.
        Add the beef or pork cube, tomato sauce, and water and let boil. Simmer for 20 minutes.
        Put the carrots and potatoes in then stir until every ingredient is properly distributed. Simmer for 10 to 12 minutes.
        Add salt, ground black pepper, and sugar then stir.
        Put in the boiled eggs and turn off the heat.
    </string>
</resources>